<idea-plugin>
  <id>MapStructMappingTool</id>
  <name>MapStructMappingTool</name>
  <version>1.0.1</version>
  <vendor email="wutailong11062@hellobike.com" url="">wutailong</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
      This will help you get the object->object mapping relationship quickly and conveniently, and generate the field mapping code corresponding to MapStruct.
      <br/>github：<a href="https://github.com/Aumin/MapStructMappingTools">https://github.com/Aumin/MapStructMappingTools</a>
      <br/>help doc：See the source code for details.README.md<br>
      <ul>
          <li>How to use: Double-click the method that needs to be mapped in the mapping class marked as maintained by MapperStruct, then right-click to select the pop-up MapStructMappingTool function bar, and the class field tree of sourceObject and targetObject can pop up, manually specify the field mapping relationship, and click after mapping. The output button outputs the automatically generated mapping code above the corresponding mapping method</li>
          <li>Usage scenario: When you need to maintain the MapStruct mapping class, you need to manually write the field mapping relationship. It may help you do these tasks more conveniently or more comfortably.
               Some special scenarios:
               1. When the meaning of the field is the same but the name of the field is different, we need to jump back and forth in the corresponding class file to confirm the field name, and write something like "@Mapping(source = "xxx", target = " xxx") code;
               2. There are many fields that require you to write the mapping relationship. The target attribute of the mapping is named the same as the source attribute, but the corresponding field level is located in a deeper position. At this time, we should pay extra attention to whether the corresponding hierarchical relationship is correct.
               3. Your project may be forced not to use MapStruct's implicit conversion capabilities
          </li>
          <li>Precautions for use: It must be marked with @Mapper, currently only for the mapping relationship of 1->1, and the mapping relationship of 1->n is not supported for the time being.</li>
      </ul>
      <br/>Finally: if you encounter problems with use, please contact me，email="wutailong11062@hellobike.com"<br>
    ]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>V1.0.0</h3>
      <br/>Beta version released<br>
      <h3>V1.0.1</h3>
      <br/>Add user guide<br>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <!-- please see https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/build-number-ranges.html for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="173.0"/>

  <!-- please see https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-compatibility.html
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>


  <actions>
    <!-- Add your actions here -->
    <action id="MapStructMappingID" class="MapStructMappingToolsAction" text="MapStructMappingTool"
            description="MapStruct代码映射工具" icon="/META-INF/icon.svg">
      <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="first"/>
      <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="shift meta M"/>
    </action>
  </actions>


</idea-plugin>